A Finding Aid to the Tibor de Nagy Gallery Records, 1941-2016, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Business Records and Correspondence, 1950-1993; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 10 Linear feet Boxes 1-10
  - Clients and Colleagues, 1950-1992; 1.2; Archival Resource Key; 0.6 Linear feet Box 3
    - Mazoh, Stephen, 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - McCoy, Jason, 1970-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - McGinnis, Patrick, 1957-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Merrill, James, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Michener, James, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Mones, Arthur, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Moynihan, Rodrigo, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Nathanson, Richard, 1975-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Neumann, Morton, 1981-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Penney, Charles, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Picarello, Frank, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Rankine, E.R., 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Ratliff, Marcus, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Rauh, Marjory, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Saionz, John, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Sciandra, Gian, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Skidmore, Owings and Merrill, 1961-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Stambler, Arthur, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Warren, Paul, Visual Resources, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Workman, David, 1966-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Zuckerman, Mrs. A., 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Publicity and Advertising, 1956-1989; 1.3; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Box 4
    Correspondence and records regarding publication advertisements and publicity for the gallery. Enclosures include price lists and mock-ups of ads, as well as mailing lists and clippings. Some articles and brief essays about the gallery and upcoming exhibitions are also included. Publications and periodicals include the New York Times, Art International, Harper's Bazaar, and radio station WNCN 104.3.
    - 57th Street Review, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - American Artist, 1975-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Art and Artists, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Art Express, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Art Forum, 1966-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Art Gallery, 1959-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Art in America, 1961-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Art International, 1960-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Art News, 1956-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Arts Magazine, 1969-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Artscribe, 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bruder Rosenbaum Wien, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1961-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Gallery Listings, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Gallery Listings, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Harper's Bazaar Article by John Myers, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Horizon, 1966-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - House and Garden, 1986, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Metro, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Mosscolor Corporation, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The New Criterion, 1982-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - New Woman, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - New York Art Review, 1982-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - New York Times, 1956-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Profile Press, 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Publications, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
    - WNCN 104.3 FM, 1970-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Records, 1957-1988; 1.4; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Boxes 4-5, 46
    Records and correspondence reflecting the day-to-day operations of the gallery and business procedures. Included are leases and construction documents for the various premises occupied by the gallery such as floor plans, maintenance, transfers, renovations and restoration. Other documents include employment records and resumes, an incorporation memo, insurance documentation and appraisals, security systems, a visitors book, and orders for framing artworks.
    - 9 West 57th Street, Proposed Gallery Center, Huberth and Peters, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 27-29 West 57th Street, Construction, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Scope and Contents note
      Oversized material housed in OV 46.
    - 27-29 West 57th Street, Leases, Cushman and Wakefield, 1969-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 27-29 West 57th Street, Leases, Landlord and Legal, 1982-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
    - 29 West 57th Street, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 29 West 57th Street, Lease, Maintenance, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 29 West 57th Street, Renovation 4th Floor, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 149 East 72nd Street, Construction, Morse and Grossman, Inc., 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 149 East 72nd Street, Lease and Restoration, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - APF, Inc., 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Appraisals, 1961-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40-43)
    - Artists' Contracts, Sample Forms, 1970-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Business Addresses, Cards, circa 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cirker's Hayes Storage Warehouse, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Employment, Resumes, 1970-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
    - Framemakers, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Incorporation Memo, circa 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Insurance, Fine Arts, 1961-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Insurance, Property and Fine Art, 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
    - Interns, 1982-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - Kulicke Frames, 1966-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Liquidation Fund, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Operations and Maintenance, 1960-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Property Maintenance, 1957-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Security, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Visitors Book, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Oversized architectural plan from Box 4, Folder 30, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1951-1993; 1.5; Archival Resource Key; 5.5 Linear feet Boxes 5-10
    Various correspondence about day to day operations and inquiries, as well as miscellaneous correspondence and mailing lists.
    Arranged chronologically, then by general alphabetical order, followed by mailing lists. Mailing lists are physically arranged as the cartons and folders best fit within the box.
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1978-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19-27)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1-20)
    - Chronological Correspondence, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
    - A, 1959-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
    - B, 1959-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
    - C, 1959-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
    - D, 1955-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
    - E, 1964-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Ex-Artists, 1952-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - F, 1958-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - G, 1969-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - H, 1959-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
    - Hungarian Artists, 1967-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - I, 1961-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - J, 1959-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - K, 1959-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - L, 1958-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - M, 1959-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14-16)
    - N, 1957-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - N, 1957-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - O, 1955-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Old Artists, 1951-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - P, 1959-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
    - Parties, 1958-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Q, 1965-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - R, 1955-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
    - Referendum 691-1800, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - S, 1960-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12-15)
    - T, 1957-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - U, 1964-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - V, 1961-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - W, 1958-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-21)
    - XYZ, 1961-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Mailing Lists, 1966-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Mailing Lists, Globe Mail Agency, 1974-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Mailing Lists, M. Gancel Co., 1971-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Mailing Cards, A-Z and Foreign List, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Carton 4-5)
    - Mailing Cards, A-Z, Artist Cards and Foreign List, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Carton 6-7)
- Exhibition Files, 1941-1992; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Boxes 11-12; 3.26 Gigabytes ER01
  This series documents various exhibitions held at the Gallery as group shows, individual artist exhibitions, and retrospectives. Exhibition materials include clippings and research materials, exhibition catalogs, exhibit and gallery plans, correspondence, and photographs, including some in digital format. Some loan agreements and shipping receipts are also included.
  Arranged chronologically by date of exhibition.
  - "13 Ways of Looking at a Blackbird" (1964), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Homage to Antonio Machado" (1966), 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Homage to Antonio Machado" (1966), 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Homage to Antonio Machado" (1966), 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, Benefit Show of Drawings (1965-1966), circa 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1965-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "Distillation" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - "Abstract Illusionism," Elizabeth Greenleaf, David Paul, Herbert Perr, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Group Show (1968), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Venice Biennale, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Schedules, 1972-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11-20)
  - "New Talent Festival" (1974), 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - "The Avant Garde in Hungary", 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - "Shape and Field" (1978), 1964-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - "Drawings of Pleasure" (1979), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - "Pattern Painting" (1979), 1978-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Sculpture Invitational, 1980-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "Artifacts at the End of a Decade" (1981), Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - "The Broken Surface" (1981), 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Catalog, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Catalog Introduction, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Checklist, Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Chronology, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Correspondence, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Giveaways, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Golubov's Correspondence, 1941-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Golubov's Records and Memorabilia, 1946-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Loans, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Loans, N.A. or Negative, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Publicity, 1944-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Refusals, Tour, 1979-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "Maurice Golubov Paintings 1925-1980" (1981), Restoration Framing and Shipping, Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "The Figure" (1982), 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Group Show, "3:1" (1982), 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - "Fact and Fiction" (1984), 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - "Abstract / Issues" (1985), 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - "Abstract / Issues" (1985), 1985-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Manifestations of the Figure" (1985), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Digital Explorations, Emerging Visions in Art" (1988), 1981-1990; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER01. (Box 12, Folder 18-21)
  - "Digital Explorations, Emerging Visions in Art" (1988), Digital Photographs, Archival Resource Key; 3.26 Gigabytes 78 computer files. (Folder ER01)
  - "Works on Paper" (1988), 1971-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - "Color as a Subject" (1992), 1980-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Artist Files, 1956-1993; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 18.6 Linear feet Boxes 13-31, 46
  These files comprise both daily business materials and collected information on artists. Typically, there are several files on each artist which may include announcements, biographies, business (including consignment, loans, and sales), catalogs, correspondence, photographic material, publicity, and reviews. Among the material on Walter Darby Bannard are three metal printing plates. Some of the more extensively covered artists include Rosemarie Castoro, Ray Ciarrocchi, Robert Goodnough, Harold Gregor, Red Grooms (including a transcript of "A Conversation with Marison and Red Grooms"), Joyce Kozloff, Peter Reginato, Tony Robbin, Leatrice Rose, and Nancy Witteman-Widrig.
  Arranged alphabetically by artists' name.
  - Altoon, John, 1967-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1-7)
  - Andre, Carl, 1965-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8-12)
  - Avery, Milton, 1974-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
  - Bannard, Walter Darby, 1955-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15-27)
  - Beale, Sondra, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Blaine, Nell, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Boterf, Chester, 1968-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Bowling, Frank, 1974-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 31-32)
  - Bowman, Ken, 1970-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1-8)
  - Boxer, Stanley, 1968-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9-16)
  - Brody, Joel, 1964-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17-19)
  - Budd, David, 1969-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20-23)
  - Bultman, Fritz, 1963-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Caro, Anthony, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Castoro, Rosemarie - General, Invoices, 1970-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Castoro, Rosemarie - Announcements and Catalogs, 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Castoro, Rosemarie - Announcements and Catalogs, 1980-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Castoro, Rosemarie - Correspondence, 1971-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Castoro, Rosemarie - Correspondence, 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Castoro, Rosemarie - Slides, 1970-1978, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ciarrocchi, Ray, 1971-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8-16)
  - Cody, Bruce, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Cohen, Larry, 1973-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18-19)
  - Cohen, Larry, 1973-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
  - Cornell, Joseph, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Cooney-Crawford, Thom, 1980-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7-12)
  - Davenport, Davy, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Ron, 1967-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
  - De Kooning, Elaine, 1981, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Downing, Thomas, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Drexler, Sherman, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Dzubas, Friedel, 1975-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Ehrlich, David, 1970-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Evans, Garth, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21-23)
  - Fauteux, Andre, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Feldstein, Mark, 1968-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Forakis, Peter, 1961-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Forsman, Chuck, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Francis, Sherron, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 28-32)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 1960-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Getz, Ilse, 1962-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Goodnough, Robert - Articles By and About, circa 1962-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Goodnough, Robert - Bio, General, 1961-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Goodnough, Robert - Business, 1958-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Goodnough, Robert - Correspondence, 1965-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Goodnough, Robert, 1959-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-8)
  - Gorchov, Ron, 1959-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
  - Gordon, Harvey, 1970-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Gourevitch, Jacqueline, 1966-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12-16)
  - Greenleaf, Ken, 1973-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17-21)
  - Gregor, Harold, 1975-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
  - Gregor, Harold, 1973-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1-16)
  - Grillo, John, 1970-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
  - Grooms, Red, 1961-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
  - Gross, Jim, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Harmon, Mary Anne, 1973-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1957-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Hennessey, Timothy, 1961-1963, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Hirsch, Gilah, 1970-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
  - Hood, Dorothy, 1970-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 12-15)
  - Hornak, Ian, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16-21)
  - Hudson, Andrew, 1971-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 22-24)
  - Hudson, Andrew, 1971-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1-7)
  - Hughto, Darryl, Biographical Information, 1970-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Hughto, Darryl, Correspondence, 1970-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Hughto, Darryl, Correspondence, 1974-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hughto, Darryl, Exhibition Announcements and Clippings, 1972-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Hughto, Darryl, Photographs and Negatives, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Hughto, Darryl, Slides of Artwork, 1973-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Hunter, Paul, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Jarden, Richards, 1979-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
  - Johnson, Ray, 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Jones, Christopher, 1983-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Kalina, Richard, 1977-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 19-22)
  - Kalina, Richard, 1977-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Kirschen-Cole, Stephanie, 1977-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, 1970-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7-15)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, 1970-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1-16)
  - Lasker, Jonathan, circa 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
  - LeComte, Mia, 1966-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 6-8)
  - Lerner, Leslie, 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - Liebert, George, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Lorentzen, Ida, 1979-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 12-18)
  - Magistro, Chuck, 1978-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 19-24)
  - Mahdavi, Rafael, 1973-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 25-27)
  - Mahdavi, Rafael, 1973-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1-5)
  - Marshall, Dan, 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  - Merchant, Yolanda, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Michod, Susan, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Milkowski, Antoni, 1966-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 10-11)
  - Miller, Mariann Loveland, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 12-15)
  - Moses, Forrest, 1974-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 16-25)
  - Motherwell, Robert, 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mueller, Stephen, 1971-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2-5)
  - Muller, Yvonne, 1976-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 6-10)
  - Nesbit, Lowell, 1974-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Nick, George, 1969-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 12-20)
  - Noland, Kenneth, 1970-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk, Geoffrey, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
  - Ostlihn, Babro, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Patterson, Patricia, 1980-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 25-27)